investmentguruindia.com 2013-10-01

# Investment Guru Stocks Mutual Funds Commodity Currency World Market Expert Advice Free Tips Recommendation

**Our Commitment**  
_investmentguruindia.com_ is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal and financial information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information.

**Information collected by** ** _investmentguruindia.com_ and how it is used**  
_investmentguruindia.com_ only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. _investmentguruindia.com_ and its service partners use your personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from _investmentguruindia.com_ and its affiliates.

_investmentguruindia.com_ may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site's service but are not necessary to its operation (an "Extended Service"). If _investmentguruindia.com_ intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the _investmentguruindia.com_ site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from _investmentguruindia.com_ by following the instructions on the mail.

_investmentguruindia.com_ may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site-owners, the site or the users of _investmentguruindia.com_ , and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of _investmentguruindia.com_ , the site, its owners, or the public.

**User/member interaction features**  
_investmentguruindia.com_ has many features that provide for users/members to disclose their identities and communicate with other users/members. Your use of such features and disclosure of any personal details (e.g. e-mail address) by you through these features are at your sole risk and _investmentguruindia.com_ accepts no responsibility for the same. However, if your privacy has been intruded as a result of participating in such features, you could notify us by e-mail at feedback@investmentguruindia.com.

**Other Websites**  
The _investmentguruindia.com_ site contains links to other websites. _investmentguruindia.com_ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Notify Us**  
If at any time you believe that _investmentguruindia.com_ or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify _investmentguruindia.com_ by e-mail at feedback@investmentguruindia.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
